(Lee Jae In, Kim Woo Seok, Choi Ye Bin)
(Cha Woo Min, An Ji Ho, Jung So Ri)
(Night Has Come)
(All people, organizations, locations, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
Take responsibility for what you said now.
Are you the Police?
Na Hee.
I'm sorry. I was fooled by So Mi too.
I knew you were not the Mafia.
No. You're the same.
No, Na Hee.
I knew that you were not the Mafia. I believed in you.
What the heck is going on?
No. Something must be wrong.
Is that a reason why you used me?
- To kill Kyung Jun? - Hey.
Yes, you crazy witch.
You said we should steal the key first.
Did you kill Kyung Jun as well?
- No. - The heck...
You did that to Eun Ha when you were the Mafia?
If it hadn't been for you, she wouldn't have died.
How can you do that if you're a human?
I had no choice.
I just wanted to survive. Why?
I didn't want to become the freaking Mafia either.
Stop with your nonsense.
Does it not matter as long as you survive?
What about us? Do we deserve to die?
Do we?
I didn't kill anyone.
The other guys killed them.
What happened to Se Eun has nothing to do with me.
Hey.
Don't use Se Eun for your own sake.
You don't deserve to do that.
Who are you to say that?
No one believes you now.
- Shut up. - Hey.
Enough.
Jun Hee.
Save me. Please.
Take responsibility as you said.
- Kim Jun Hee... - No.
voted for Kim So Mi.
- No. - Oh Jung Won...
- Hold on. - voted for Kim So Mi.
- Don't do it. - Ahn Na Hee...
- voted for Kim So Mi. - Don't vote.
Give me the phone.
- Give me the phone. - Just stop.
You're all fooled.
Do you know who the Mafias are?
You can't reveal the identities of other Mafias to Citizens.
Darn it.
You're doing all sorts of things.
Hey.
Just die.
Im Eun Chan voted for Kim So Mi.
Nam Yeon Woo voted for Kim So Mi.
Why did you do that?
You brought it on yourself.
(Will you vote for Kim So Mi?)
Lee Yoon Seo voted for Kim So Mi.
We need to hide. Let's hurry up and go.
- Se Eun. - Voting is over.
With the most votes, Kim So Mi will be executed.
(Ahn Na Hee is a Police Officer.)
(You can find out the identity of a selected participant.)
(Jang Hyun Ho)
(Will you use your Skill on Jang Hyun Ho?)
(Yes.)
(Jang Hyun Ho is a Citizen.)
Hyun Ho.
I know...
your identity.
(Will you use your Skill on Kim Jun Hee?)
(Kim Jun Hee is a Citizen.)
Yes, it's me. I'm the Mafia.
Just vote for that jerk and end this!
(Kim Jun Hee)
(Jun Hee is a Citizen. From Police)
It's just you and me now.
Let's deal with the Police first.
(Be mindful of your safety when cleaning the pool!)
Yoon Seo.
Wake up, Yoon Seo.
What's the matter? Did you have a dream?
During the night, Ahn Na Hee...
was executed by the Mafia.
Ahn Na Hee was a Police Officer.
All participants,
identify the Mafia and begin to vote.
No.
Darn it!
Why?
What do we do with Na Hee?
There's no Police now.
How can we find the Mafias?
We found out who had spread the rumor about Se Eun.
Why is the game not over?
Do we have to find all the Mafias to end this game?
I don't know either.
Oh, gosh.
Hey.
Se Eun!
There aren't many of us now.
What do we do?
Where are the other guys?
Are they upstairs?
I didn't see them.
Mi Na and Da Bum...
are nowhere to be seen.
Are they planning a strategy?
The three of them stole the key.
Those jerks.
Who are they going to kill this time?
Hey.
Don't we have to prepare something as well?
Prepare what?
We should do something to stop the Mafias from killing us.
We should tie our limbs while sleeping...
so that no one can move. We should do something like that at least.
Let's talk about it when everyone gathers.
Did you get changed?
- Why? - What's the matter?
You told me how to find blood last time.
I want to find this instead of blood.
Na Hee asked me...
to find out who killed her...
if she died.
I don't know who I should trust. So I called you out only.
The Mafias will come to kill me first.
Help me.
Okay, I will.
Let's hide first.
Not that.
Help me find out who they are.
What?
Just like how Yoon Seo identified the footprint,
if we're prepared beforehand...
to figure out the identity of Mafias when they came to kill me,
you will be able to find out.
I had many chances,
but I ruined them all.
If I had used my Skill as the Police,
I would've saved the others.
I ruined everything.
Jun Hee.
I want to do it properly this time.
Thank you, Jun Hee.
I'll come to take you in the morning.
See you tomorrow.
We mixed air freshener with neon paint.
The one who killed Na Hee must have the paint on their shoes.
(Jin Da Bum)
Did Na Hee really ask you to do this?
- It's not a lie? - Right.
Na Hee's dead too.
How can we believe you?
Do you believe me now?
There's no reason to object if you're not Mafia.
Am I wrong?
Does that actually work?
What's this? Why is it glowing?
It's her.
No wonder.
I found it weird when she wanted to steal Kyung Jun's keys.
No, this isn't right. It wasn't me.
Did you kill Na Hee?
I didn't kill her!
How could I kill her when I didn't know where she was?
Why is it on your shoe if you didn't kill her?
How the heck would I know that?
I'm a Citizen.
- Can you prove it? - What?
Is there proof...
you're a Citizen?
I think we found a Mafia.
Let's vote now.
Have you all lost your minds?
It's not me. I'm a Citizen.
We agreed to vote tonight.
Why?
Why wait when we're sure it's her?
Let's vote now.
Get your hands off me!
How many times must I say it wasn't me?
You haven't yet explained how you took Kyung Jun's keys.
So Mi put me up to...
As if she did.
You tried to gang up on me and kill me.
No.
So Mi used me just the same.
Let's calm down.
Give me that.
Show me the bottom.
If she were really there,
the paint would be on the bottom too.
It's weird how it's just a bit to the side.
Someone could've got it on her. We can't be sure.
(Jin Da Bum)
Yes.
Let's vote tonight as planned.
We should vote when we're all up for it.
Jun Hee.
- Get the light. - Okay.
(Keep off during daytime)
Look.
The paint's everywhere,
but there was just a drop on Mi Na's shoe.
Everyone else's shoes were clean.
The Mafia could've come in barefoot.
(Oh Jung Won)
That's possible.
Look at this. There's something here.
Step down for a second.
- Turn on the light. - Okay.
It's blood.
Blood?
Yes.
I'd say someone was badly hurt.
Na Hee had no wounds.
Then...
whose blood is that?
Can you go check on Mi Na?
I'll talk to Jun Hee.
Okay.
Jun Hee.
(Muryeong Retreat Center)
The Mafia could've gotten hurt while looking for Na Hee.
I don't think...
it's right to corner Mi Na because of her shoes.
Okay.
We'll check,
but if we don't find anything,
we'll vote for Mi Na anyway.
Jun Hee.
The Mafia could be using her like they did Jin Ha.
We'll miss out on getting them again.
The evidence points to Mi Na right now.
We can't let the Mafia be in control forever.
Jun Hee.
I'm sick of seeing people die.
Let's get out of here.
Let's go home, Yoon Seo.
If it's only on her shoe,
then it must be her.
Darn Yoon Seo.
My point exactly.
What's the point in waiting until tonight?
Why are you here?
I brought some food...
because I thought you'd be hungry.
My gosh...
Are you hungry, Yeon Woo?
Have some ramyeon.
Get lost!
You got soup all over your shoes.
What are you doing?
I don't mind.
Yeon Woo, I swear I'm not Mafia.
I really am not. Will you help me out?
Shouldn't you believe me at least?
We used to be friends.
Don't vote for me, Eun Chan.
I'm not Mafia.
You and So Mi made Eun Ha look like Mafia and killed her!
No, that was because she said we should vote for Yul.
I had no choice but to vote. I'm really not Mafia.
Guys, let's talk. Will you hear me out?
- Get lost! Go! - Please.
What jerks.
Wait and see what I do.
Choi Mi Na.
You mean...
the person who got hurt in the toilet is the Mafia?
Yes.
We're not sure yet, so keep it to yourself.
Don't tell the others.
Okay.
Hey, look over my body. I have no wounds.
Look. I wasn't hurt.
- I'm really not... - Okay.
I got it.
Thanks for helping me, Jung Won.
I really wanted to be friends with you.
And Yoon Seo too.
Just like that?
No. I'd wanted to be friends for a long time.
It feels like I finally got to know you.
It's so nice.
You should keep this.
I'll just follow you around.
Why give me this?
Because we're both Citizens.
Why would I give it to you if I were the Mafia?
I'm not stupid.
Will you believe me just this once, Jung Won?
I'm not the Mafia.
I didn't see any wounds on Mi Na's body.
We talked for a while and I didn't notice anything odd.
I'll check the others.
The Mafia kept deceiving us.
How about...
we do the same?
What?
How?
What if we say we found a camera Na Hee set up in secret,
but it's dead so we're charging it?
They'll do anything to destroy it like they did the camera footage.
We found a camera Na Hee set up before she died.
We're charging it and we'll soon find out who's Mafia.
Let's meet up in 30 minutes.
(We found a camera Na Hee set up before she died.)
(We're charging it and we'll soon find out who's Mafia.)
(Let's meet up in 30 minutes.)
(Kim Jun Hee)
(Jin Da Bum)
We'll separate the two most suspicious people...
and create a situation.
They'll have to show themselves.
Do you think it'll work?
We must force them to make a move.
Yes.
Let's do it.
Hey.
Where's the camera?
Oh, we're charging it in the cafeteria.
I'll go out for a bit.
Okay. See you.
Darn it.
Let's wait in the cafeteria.
Is it done charging?
Where do we meet?
In the cafeteria.
We're on our way now.
I'll come with you.
Where's Nam Yeon Woo?
He went to the infirmary saying he felt sick.
The person who got hurt in the toilet is the Mafia?
Yes.
Get your hands off me!
Look.
Why would you check...
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Let's see.
Look at this.
Nam Yeon Woo.
What's that cut?
It's nothing.
(Jin Da Bum)
(No file)
Why is it blank?
What's that cut?
I got hurt.
Why? Were you afraid it caught you?
No, it's not that.
Something's not right.
Get over here, Mafia scum.
- You psycho! - Let him go.
Guys, it's not like that.
It's not.
Darn it.
You say that after you saw his stomach?
It wasn't me!
Will you hear me out?
What's going on?
Why should we listen? You're the Mafia.
There's a gash on Yeon Woo's body.
It wasn't me.
It's not me. I swear.
(Night Has Come)
(Gwangju Information and Content Agency)
(This content was produced through Gwangju Information and...)
(Content Agency's 2022 OTT Platform Content Production Business.)